<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic SYSTEM "../../../../lib/pkp/dtd/helpTopic.dtd">

<!--
  * 000003.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2005-2012 Alec Smecher and John Willinsky
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Administrative Functions Help Page 
  *
  * $Id$
  -->

<topic id="admin/topic/000003" locale="en_US" title="Administrative Functions" toc="admin/toc/000000" key="admin.administrativeFunctions">
	<section title="System Information">
		<![CDATA[<p>The System Information page provides information about the Open Harvester Systems installation, including versions, configuration information, and server information. The "Check for updates" link allows the administrator to determine whether their Open Harvester Systems installation is up-to-date; it is recommended that Administrators update the application whenever possible to ensure that their installation is secure and bug-free. Release information will also be made available on the <a href="http://pkp.sfu.ca" target="_new">PKP web site</a> and the <a href="http://pkp.sfu.ca/support/forum" target="_new">support forum</a>.</p>
		<p><strong>System Configuration:</strong> The Open Harvester Systems Configuration page can be reached from the System Information page by following the "Edit" link under Open Harvester Systems Configuration. This feature allows the Administrator to edit the Open Harvester Systems configuration file, config.inc.php, using a web-based form. Entering the wrong values may render the Open Harvester Systems installation inoperable; this feature is recommended for use only by advanced users.</p><p>More information on the configuration file can be found in the documents distributed with the Open Harvester Systems installation. See config.TEMPLATE.inc.php and docs/README for more information.</p>
		<p><strong>Server Information:</strong> extended server information (OS platform; PHP version; Apache version; Database driver and version, as well as a link to phpinfo(); output) can be found at the very bottom of the System Information Page.</p>]]>
	</section>
	<section title="Expire User Sessions">
		<![CDATA[<p>Clicking the Expire User Sessions link invalidates all sessions, forcing the administrator to log in again.</p>]]>
	</section>
	<section title="Clear Data Caches">
		<![CDATA[<p>Clicking the Clear Data Caches link destroys all cached data, including search caches and locale data caches.</p>]]>
	</section>
	<section title="Clear Template Cache">
		<![CDATA[<p>Clicking the Clear Template Cache link estroys all compiled templates, forcing a re-compile upon next use.</p>]]>
	</section>
</topic>
